<quotes>

<quote>
<msg>You must be the change you wish to see in the world.</msg>
<id>0</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong.</msg>
<id>1</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Live as if you were to die tomorrow; learn as if you were to live forever.</msg>
<id>2</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony.</msg>
<id>3</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>An eye for eye only ends up making the whole world blind.</msg>
<id>4</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Nobody can hurt me without my permission.</msg>
<id>5</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.</msg>
<id>6</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A man is but the product of his thoughts; what he thinks, he becomes.</msg>
<id>7</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>First they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they fight you, then you win.</msg>
<id>8</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will.</msg>
<id>9</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>Hate the sin, love the sinner.</msg>
<id>10</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The good man is the friend of all living things.</msg>
<id>11</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Civilization is the encouragement of differences.</msg>
<id>12</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>No culture can live, if it attempts to be exclusive.</msg>
<id>13</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>That service is the noblest which is rendered for its own sake.</msg>
<id>14</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Whenever you are confronted with an opponent, conquer him with love.</msg>
<id>15</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong.</msg>
<id>16</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.</msg>
<id>17</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Service which is rendered without joy helps neither the servant nor the served.</msg>
<id>18</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Whatever you do will be insignificant, but it is very important that you do it.</msg>
<id>19</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>Those who cannot renounce attachment to the results of their work are far from the path.</msg>
<id>20</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Action expresses priorities.</msg>
<id>21</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Nonviolence is a weapon of the strong.</msg>
<id>22</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>To lose patience is to lose the battle.</msg>
<id>23</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The future depends on what you do today.</msg>
<id>24</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>An ounce of practice is worth a thousand words.</msg>
<id>25</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>It is difficult, but not impossible, to conduct strictly honest business</msg>
<id>26</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>If I have the belief that I can do it, I shall surely acquire the capacity to do it even if I may not have it at the beginning.</msg>
<id>27</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.</msg>
<id>28</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Victory attained by violence is tantamount to a defeat, for it is momentary.</msg>
<id>29</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>First they ignore you, then laugh at you, then they fight you, then you win.</msg>
<id>30</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Honest differences are often a healthy sign of progress.</msg>
<id>31</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will.</msg>
<id>32</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Be the change you want to see in the world.</msg>
<id>33</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>God has no religion.</msg>
<id>34</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The one religion is beyond all speech.</msg>
<id>35</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Even if you are a minority of one, the truth is the truth.</msg>
<id>36</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Prayer is the key of the morning and the bolt of the evening.</msg>
<id>37</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Faith is put to the test when the situation is most difficult.</msg>
<id>38</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>As long as you derive inner help and comfort from anything, keep it.</msg>
<id>39</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>Faith becomes lame, when it ventures into matters pertaining to reason!</msg>
<id>40</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>I believe in the fundamental truth of all great religions of the world.</msg>
<id>41</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A leader is useless when he acts against the promptings of his own conscience.</msg>
<id>42</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>In matters of conscience, the law of the majority has no place.</msg>
<id>43</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>It is easy enough to be friendly to one’s friends but to befriend one who regards himself as your enemy is the quintessence of true religion.</msg>
<id>44</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>To retaliate against the relatives of the co-religionists of the wrong-doer is a cowardly act.</msg>
<id>45</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Ashram means a community of men of religion. I feel that an ashram was a necessity of life for me.</msg>
<id>46</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Religion is a matter of the heart. No physical inconvenience can warrant abandonment of one’s own religion.</msg>
<id>47</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The difference between what we do and what we are capable of doing would suffice to solve most of the world’s problem.</msg>
<id>48</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>You may never know what results come of your action, but if you do nothing there will be no result.</msg>
<id>49</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.</msg>
<id>50</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A ‘No’ uttered from the deepest conviction is better than a ‘Yes’ merely uttered to please, or worse, to avoid trouble.</msg>
<id>51</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Freedom is not worth having if it does not include the freedom to make mistakes.</msg>
<id>52</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony.</msg>
<id>53</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>You can chain me, you can torture me, you can even destroy this body, but you will never imprison my mind.</msg>
<id>54</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>If you want real peace in the world, start with children.</msg>
<id>55</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Intolerance is itself a form of violence and an obstacle to the growth of a true democratic spirit.</msg>
<id>56</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Freedom is not worth having if it does not include the freedom to make mistakes.</msg>
<id>57</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>It is unwise to be too sure of ones own wisdom. It is healthy to be reminded that the strongest might weaken and the wisest might err.</msg>
<id>58</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>God has given me no control over the following moment. I am concerned about taking care of the present.</msg>
<id>59</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>An ounce of practice is worth a thousand words.</msg>
<id>60</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Have faith in humanity. Humanity is like an ocean; if a few drops of the ocean are dirty, the whole ocean doesn’t become dirty.</msg>
<id>61</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony.</msg>
<id>62</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A leader is useless when he acts against the promptings of his own conscience.</msg>
<id>63</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>To believe in something, and not to live it, is dishonest.</msg>
<id>64</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>I have no disciples, being myself an aspirant after discipleship and in search of a guru.</msg>
<id>65</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The hardest heart and the grossest ignorance must disappear before the rising sun of suffering without anger and without malice.</msg>
<id>66</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>I believe that there is no prayer without fasting and there is no real fast without prayer.</msg>
<id>67</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>It is better to be violent, if there is violence in our hearts, than to put on the cloak of nonviolence to cover impotence.</msg>
<id>68</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony.</msg>
<id>69</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>Your beliefs become your thoughts, Your thoughts become your words, Your words become your actions, Your actions become your habits, Your habits become your values, Your values become your destiny.</msg>
<id>70</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>An eye for an eye will only make the whole world blind.</msg>
<id>71</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.</msg>
<id>72</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Freedom is not worth having if it does not include the freedom to make mistakes.</msg>
<id>73</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Always aim at complete harmony of thought and word and deed. Always aim at purifying your thoughts and everything will be well.</msg>
<id>74</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>One can measure the greatness and the moral progress of a nation by looking at how it treats its animals.</msg>
<id>75</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>I wish to change there minds, not kill them for weaknesses we all poses.</msg>
<id>76</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Earth provides enough to satisfy every man’s needs, but not even one man’s greed.</msg>
<id>77</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>To give pleasure to a single heart by a single act is better than a thousand heads bowing in prayer.</msg>
<id>78</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Freedom is not worth having if it does not include the freedom to make mistakes.</msg>
<id>79</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>An error does not become truth by reason of multiplied propagation, nor does truth become error because nobody sees it.</msg>
<id>80</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.</msg>
<id>81</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Prayer is the key of the morning and the bolt of the evening.</msg>
<id>82</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Even if you are a minority of one, the truth is the truth.</msg>
<id>83</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A man is but the product of his thoughts what he thinks, he becomes.</msg>
<id>84</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Among the many misdeeds of the British rule in India, history will look upon the act depriving a whole nation of arms as the blackest.</msg>
<id>85</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Always aim at complete harmony of thought and word and deed, always aim at purifying your thoughts and everything will be well.</msg>
<id>86</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A small body of determined spirits fired by an unquenchable faith in their mission can alter the course of history.</msg>
<id>87</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A principle is the expression of perfection, and as imperfect beings like us cannot practise perfection, we devise every moment limits of its compromise in practice.</msg>
<id>88</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Faith becomes lame, when it ventures into matters pertaining to reason!</msg>
<id>89</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>Fear has its use but cowardice has none.</msg>
<id>90</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>My life is my message.</msg>
<id>91</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Nobody can hurt me without my permission.</msg>
<id>92</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>All humanity is one undivided and indivisible family, and each one of us is responsible for the misdeeds of all the others.</msg>
<id>93</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Distinguish between real needs and artificial wants and control the latter.</msg>
<id>94</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Satisfaction lies in the effort, not in the attainment. Full effort is full victory.</msg>
<id>95</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>When you want to find Truth as God, the only inevitable means is love, that is nonviolence.</msg>
<id>96</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The difference between what we do and what we are capable of doing would suffice to solve most of the world’s problem.</msg>
<id>97</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>We have to handover the earth, the air, the land and the water to the children at least as it was handed over to us.</msg>
<id>98</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>As long as you derive inner help and comfort from anything, keep it.</msg>
<id>99</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>I am prepared to die, but there is no cause for which I am prepared to kill.</msg>
<id>100</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Love is the strongest force the world possesses, yet it is the humblest imaginable.</msg>
<id>101</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>You may never know what results come of your actions, but if you do nothing, there will be no results.</msg>
<id>102</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Before the throne of the Almighty, man will be judged not by his acts but by his intentions. For God alone reads our hearts.</msg>
<id>103</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Nothing has saddened me so much in life as the hardness of heart of educated people.</msg>
<id>104</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Peace between countries must rest on the solid foundation of love between individuals.</msg>
<id>105</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Power based on love is a thousand times more effective and permanent than the one derived from fear of punishment.</msg>
<id>106</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Faith is put to the test when the situation is most difficult.</msg>
<id>107</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Anger is the enemy of non-violence and pride is a monster that swallows it up.</msg>
<id>108</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Peace is the most powerful weapon of mankind.</msg>
<id>109</id>
</quote>

<quote>
<msg>To answer brutality with brutality is to admit one’s moral and intellectual bankruptcy and it can only start a viscous cycle.</msg>
<id>110</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>What is truth? A difficult question; but I have solved it for myself by saying that it is what the “Voice within” tells you.</msg>
<id>111</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>One needs to be slow to form convictions, but once formed they must be defended against the heaviest odds.</msg>
<id>112</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>A man is the sum of his actions, of what he has done, of what he can do, nothing else.</msg>
<id>113</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Freedom is never dear at any price. It is the breath of life. What would a man not pay for living?</msg>
<id>114</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>The real love is to love them that hate you, to love your neighbor even though you distrust him.</msg>
<id>115</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Non-violence requires a double faith, faith in God and also faith in man.</msg>
<id>116</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>I object to violence because when it appears to do good, the good is only temporary; the evil it does is permanent.</msg>
<id>117</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>God lives, but not as we. His creatures live but to die. But God is life. Therefore, goodness is not an attribute. Goodness is God.</msg>
<id>118</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Where there is love there is life.</msg>
<id>119</id>
</quote>


</quotes>