<quotes>

<quote>
<msg>Suffering is the essence of success.</msg>
<id>0</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Without involvement you can't succeed with your involvement you cant fail.</msg>
<id>1</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Climbing to the top demands strength, whether it is to the top of mount everest or to the top of your career</msg>
<id>2</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Don't take rest after your first victory, because if you fail in second, more lips are waiting to say that your first victory was just luck.</msg>
<id>3</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>All birds find shelter during rain. But eagle avoids rain by flying above the clouds.</msg>
<id>4</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Failures will never overtake me if my defenition to succeed is strong enough.</msg>
<id>5</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Man needs difficulties in life, Because they are necessary to enjoy the success.</msg>
<id>6</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>If you want to shine like a sun, first burn like a sun.</msg>
<id>7</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>It is very easy to defeat someone, but, it is very hard to win someone</msg>
<id>8</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>All of us do not have equal talent, but all of us have an equal opportunity to develop our talents.</msg>
<id>9</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Be more dedicated to making solid achievements than in running after but synthetic happiness.</msg>
<id>10</id>
</quote>


<quote>
<msg>The best brains of the nations may be found on the last bench of the classroom.</msg>
<id>11</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>THINKING should become your capital asset. No matter whatever ups and downs you come across in your life.</msg>
<id>12</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>You have to dream before your dreams can come true.</msg>
<id>13</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Excellence is continuos process and not an accident.</msg>
<id>14</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Life is a difficult game. You can win it only by retaining your brightness to be a person.</msg>
<id>15</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>You cant change your future, but you can change your habbits and surely your habbits will change your future.</msg>
<id>16</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Dont read success stories, you will only get a message. Read failure stories, you will get some ideas to get success.</msg>
<id>17</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>When your SIGNATURE changes to your AUTOGRAPH, this marks the success.</msg>
<id>18</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>End is not the end, infact END means, Effort Never Dies.</msg>
<id>19</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>If you fail, never give up, because, FAIL means First Attempt In Learning.</msg>
<id>20</id>
</quote>


<quote>
<msg>Love your job, but don't love your company, because you may not know when your company stops loving you.</msg>
<id>21</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Life is a difficult game. You can win it only by retaining your birthright to be a person.</msg>
<id>22</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>We should not give up and we should not allow the problem to defeat us.</msg>
<id>23</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Look at the sky. We are not alone. The whole universe is friendly to us and conspires only to give the best those who dream and work.</msg>
<id>24</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>To succeed in your mission, you must have a single minded devotion to your goal.</msg>
<id>25</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Dream, Dream, Dream. Dream transforms into thoughts and thoughts results in action.</msg>
<id>26</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>I am not a handsome guy, but I can give my hand to someone who needs help. Beauti is in the heart, not in the face.</msg>
<id>27</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>Great dreams of great dreamers are always trancended.</msg>
<id>28</id>
</quote>
<quote>
<msg>For a great man, religion is a way of making friends; small people make religion a fighting tool.</msg>
<id>29</id>
</quote>


</quotes>
